Kevin Walorz

https://github.com/kwalorz

Medfield, MA (781) 985-4659 kmwalorz@gmail.com

I am an aspiring, self taught developer with over 1 year experience creating projects with HTML, CSS, and Javascript. My main focus has been on gaining proficiency with Javascript, but I am open to learning new languages that would suit my future employer's needs.

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Frameworks: Currently learning React JS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fit Factory, North Attleboro MA

February 2020-PRESENT

Customer Service Rep

- Provide a great customer experience from when members walk in until they leave
- Take prospects on tours of facility and provide the best solution to their fitness needs

Velocity Sports Performance, Norwood MA

September 2018 - PRESENT

Sales & Marketing Manager

- Write interesting and captivating copy for email campaigns that keeps clients engaged and prospects coming through the door.
- Enhance the effectiveness of social media posts by inputting edits to images or copy
- Keep the staff up to date on the health of the business by running a monthly KPI report detailing our revenue, new member acquisition, and lost members
- Close 8–12 prospects per month, even during a major organizational change.
- Consistently maintain a 80-90% retention rate for our adult client base by staying engaged with their experience, feedback, and concerns.

Empower Retirement, Andover MA — Customer Service Rep

October 2016 - September 2018

- Serviced over 80 calls per day while keeping an upbeat attitude and connecting with our clients on a personal level.
- Retained over 2 million dollars of assets by showing clients the benefits of IRA accounts before collaborating with our asset retention team.
- Guided clients towards their financial goals by aiding them in retirement portfolio creation, 401k loans, and buying/selling investments.

EDUCATION

Bridgewater State University — *Bachelor of Arts*, *Communication Studies* September 2011 - August 2016